Room Management Using Socket.io

This system uses Socket.io for efficient room management, providing functionalities like creating, joining, leaving, and disconnecting from rooms. Additionally, it supports retrieving available rooms for players to join.

Features:
Create Room: Users can create a new room with specified settings.
Join Room: Players can join existing rooms based on availability.
Leave Room: Players can leave rooms they’re currently in.
Disconnect: Handles player disconnections and room data cleanup.
Get Available Rooms: Players can view available rooms to join.

In-Memory Storage:
The system uses Socket.io's in-memory storage for managing rooms and player data. This approach leverages the server's RAM for fast, real-time storage and retrieval of room data.

Storage Usage:

For 100 rooms, each with 4 players, the total storage requirement would be between 20 KB and 25 KB.
Room data is stored in the following format:

{
    "id": "room_abc123",      // Unique Room ID
    "name": "Room 1",          // Room Name
    "players": ["player1", "player2"], // List of players in the room
    "maxPlayers": 4,           // Maximum players allowed in the room
    "minPlayers": 2            // Minimum players required to start the game
}

Room Data Breakdown:
id: A unique identifier for the room.
name: The name of the room.
players: A list of player IDs currently in the room.
maxPlayers: The maximum number of players allowed in the room.
minPlayers: The minimum number of players required to start the game.

This setup ensures a lightweight, fast, and efficient room management system suitable for small to medium-sized multiplayer games.